Contact

209-914-7796 (Mobile) enarnincali@me.com

www.linkedin.com/in/enajarquin-40274580 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Medication Administration Critical Care ICU

Languages

English (Full Professional)
Spanish (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

ENLS BSN CCRN

TNCC

BLS

Ena Jarquin

ICU RN, BSN, CCRN, TCRN at Stanford Medical Center Tracy, California

Summary

I am currently in the ICU at Stanford Medical Center in Palo Alto CA where I care for critically ill trauma, medical, surgical, neuro, neuro trauma, neuro surgical and transplant patients. I also have previous CVICU and SICU experience working at Doctors Medical Center in Modesto CA where I cared for critically ill trauma, medical, surgical and cardiovascular patients recovering from open heart surgery. I focus on providing compassionate patient-focused care and maintaining a strong reputation for achieving high levels of patient satisfaction. I am bilingual in Spanish with excellent organizational skills. I am able to effectively and critically problem solve within a variety of clinical situations. I Successfully practice in both leadership and fellowship roles and exhibit effective listening and communication skills. I love learning and being challenged.

Experience

Stanford Health Care
BSN RN CCRN, TCRN / Clinical Nurse II
June 2016 - Present (4 years 1 month)
Stanford, Ca.

Medical / Surgical / Neuro Trauma / Neuro Surgical / Liver Transplant ICU

Doctors Medical Center -Modesto BSN RN / Clinical Nurse III January 2008 - May 2016 (8 years 5 months) Modesto, California

- Oral & IV medication administration Procedural assistance
- Blood glucose monitoring/treatment Tracheostomy suction & care
- Nasogastric tube insertion & care rectal tube insertion and management
- Ostomy care CRRT, IABP, Impella
- Urinary Catheter insertion & care Hemodynamic monitoring w/SwanGanz
- · Blood administration & collection HIPPA compliance
- Diagnostic & assessment skills Reporting & documentation

- Excellent multi-tasking skills Excellent organization & communication
- Hemodynamic monitoring & Interventions Multiple IV drip titration and management
- 12 Lead EKG Dysrhythmia identification & intervention
- Central Lines, PICC, Arterial & CVP line Ventilators, Chest tube, wound vac, pacers
- Arctic Sun Hypothermic therapy Care of pre-op/post-op, septic & trauma pt.
- Fluent in Spanish Precept of new grad. RN & RN students
- Precept & Vigaleo Wound dressing change, sterile & clean
- PCA & epidural pain management Post Angio & sheath removal
- Relief Charge

Education

The University of Texas at Arlington Bachelor's Degree, RN-BSN · (2013 - 2015)

San Joaquin Delta College

Associate's Degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2007)